(Sheldon:)I always looked up
to you and Pop-Pop.
I-I know what
a challenging man he could be,
(Sheldon:)but I saw you stand
by him and-and make him
(Sheldon:)into a better person.
(Sheldon:)I did.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, well, that is exactly
(Sheldon:)what I've been doing
the last five years
(Sheldon:)with this little
work in progress.
(Leonard:)He never disappoints,
does he?
(Amy:)I think what Sheldon means
to say is
(Amy:)we've both grown together.
(Amy:)Isn't that right?
(Sheldon:)Well...
(Penny:)Say yes.
(Penny:)Yes.
MEEMAW:
Fine.
(Meemaw:)If you feel so strongly,
I won't stand in your way.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Amy:)So if he wanted
(Amy:)to give me
that engagement ring,
(Amy:)we would have your blessing?
(Meemaw:)I suppose.
(Sheldon:)I just gave you
my virginity, woman.
(Sheldon:)Cool your jets.
(Raj:)Yeah, see, if you
just change the story
(Raj:)to the destruction
of our galaxy,
(Raj:)then a super massive
black hole could work.
(Claire:)This is great.
(Claire:)Thank you so much.
(Claire:)I just got to figure out
a way for everyone
(Claire:)to die that isn't too scary
for children.
(Raj:)And that's how
Mommy and Daddy met.
(Claire:)Hey, did you ever tell Emily
about us?
I will!